londondrugs.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy

## Safeguarding your Personal Information

**_Last updated: February 4, 2019_**

At London Drugs, we will not collect, use, or disclose your personal information without your consent - except as required or permitted by law. We do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone for any reason.

Personal information you provide to us will only be used by us as part of our ongoing efforts to provide you with superior service and selection.

We know that we earn your business and your trust with each transaction. That is why we take extensive measures designed to protect your privacy by safeguarding any personal information we collect, provide to third-party service providers and/or store during the course of doing business together. Please see also our [Security & Cookie Policy.](https://www.londondrugs.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-LondonDrugs-Site/default/Page-Show?cid=%20PrivacySecurity)

Our mandate for protecting your privacy is to ensure that our privacy standards meet or exceed the guiding principles established in federal and provincial privacy legislation.

London Drugs is responsible for personal information it holds or which is under its control, including the personal information it entrusts to service providers. We have designated a person to act as our Privacy Officer, whose duties will include monitoring London Drugs compliance with relevant legislation, replying to our valued customers’ questions, as well as responding to requests by individuals for access to and correction for any personal information London Drugs has collected on them.

_We adhere to Ten Privacy Principles to ensure your personal information is protected._

* * *

## London Drugs 10 Principles of Privacy Protection

**Principle 1 - Accountability**  
London Drugs is responsible for maintaining and protecting the customer information under its control. In fulfilling this mandate, London Drugs has designated an individual who is accountable for the Company's compliance with the Ten Privacy Principles.

**Principle 2 - Identifying Purposes**  
The purposes for which your information is collected, used or disclosed shall be identified before or at the time the information is collected, used or disclosed. We do not use or disclose personal information for reasons other than the specific purpose for which it was originally collected or consented to. London Drugs will limit the collection and use of your information to the minimum we require to deliver superior service to you, our customer; this includes advising and providing you with our products, services and other opportunities, and to administer our business.

**Principle 3 - Consent**  
Your knowledge and consent (express or implied) are required for the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information except where required or permitted by law.

**Principle 4 - Limiting Collection**  
Any personal information we collect from you is limited to those details necessary for the business transaction, as described further below, and we only collect this information using fair and lawful means.

**Principle 5 - Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention**  
We will only use or disclose your personal information for the purpose for which it was collected - unless you provide us with consent to do otherwise or when it is required or permitted by law. We will not retain your personal information any longer than required to fulfill the needs of why we collected the information.

**Principle 6 - Accuracy**  
Our commitment is to maintain your personal information as accurate, complete and up-to-date as is necessary for the purpose that we collected it for in the first place.

**Principle 7 - Safeguarding Customer Information**  
At London Drugs, we are committed to protecting your personal information with safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of that information.

**Principle 8 - Openness**  
At London Drugs, we will answer your questions about our privacy policies, procedures, and our management of your personal information in as understandable a format as possible.

**Principle 9 - Customer Access**  
If you require details on your personal information at London Drugs, please send us a written request. Upon receipt of this request, London Drugs will inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information and will provide access to that information, except where the law requires or permits London Drugs to deny access. We will provide you information within a reasonable time period and provide an explanation if we are unable to meet your request. Some inquiries may entail a charge, but we will provide an estimate for the amount in advance.

**Principle 10 - Handling Customer Complaints and Suggestions**  
Our commitment is to handle questions about our privacy principles, practices or any suggestions to improve promptly. Please direct your communications to the London Drugs Chief Privacy Officer at [privacy@londondrugs.com](mailto:privacy@londondrugs.com)

* * *

## Categories of personal information we collect, use and disclose

At London Drugs, we gather and use personal information to provide you with the services you have requested or to offer additional products and services we believe you might be interested in. Providing us with your personal information is always your choice. Most of the information we collect comes to us directly from you, and only with your consent. The types of information we may ask for depends on the nature of our service to you.

We consider personal information to include your name, address, phone number, email address, credit-card information and any other personal information that can be linked to you.

London Drugs does not intentionally collect personal information for any reason about children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 and would like to use some of the features of the Websites which involve providing personal information, please ask a parent or guardian for assistance.

**In-store purchases**  
We do not, as a condition of the supply of a product or service to you, require you to consent to the collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information beyond that information which we require to deliver superior service to you, our customer; this includes advising you about our products, services and other opportunities, and to administer our business.

We may need to collect contact and payment information from you to complete a transaction. Examples where we may need contact information includes arranging for home delivery of items you may have purchased, facilitating product repairs and servicing, performing in-home installations, facilitating manufacturers’ warranty coverage, processing rebate requests, offering service on extended warranty plans and accepting product returns.

Should we wish to use your contact information to send you promotional information, we will ask for your consent. We may also send you a thank you communication following a purchase from certain departments. This will typically be the only communication you will receive following a purchase and it is truly our way of saying thank you for your business.

**London Drugs Online Store**   
The information you provide when you make a purchase on the London Drugs Online Store is collected by London Drugs to process and fulfill your online transaction(s). When making an online purchase you will be requested to provide information including: name, phone, address, email and payment information. This information enables us to ensure that your goods are shipped to the right address and to contact you as needed in connection with your order. London Drugs does not retain credit card information unless requested to do so, in which case it is securely maintained and encrypted.

In order to protect all parties from fraudulent transactions and reduce risk of misuse of personal information, London Drugs may provide your personal information, including your address and credit card information, to reputable third party organizations to perform data verification. For example, an address verification is intended to ensure that the address provided appears valid and that the "Bill to" address matches your credit card address. 

You may sign up for an account with www.londondrugs.com so that you will not need to re-enter all the information required to complete a purchase each time you place an online order. To sign up for an account we will ask you to provide certain personal information including name, email and ask you to create a password. Registered users of the www.londondrugs.com site have the ability to view, update and change their personal profile within this site.

By signing up for an account, you may benefit from an enhanced online user experience through additional functionality and services that may only be available to registered users, such as subscription order services, improved product recommendations, personalized offers and store locator suggestions.

If you request a subscription order service, your credit card information is maintained by our processor Moneris in an encrypted and tokenized manner. Your email will be used to notify you of upcoming shipments. You may cancel or change your subscription order by logging into your account.

**E-newsletters & Personalized Use of our Websites **  
You may from time to time be given an option to receive communications from London Drugs in the form of electronic newsletters, emails or customized promotions, which relate to things such as featured products, special offers and London Drugs news, events and services. In order to enroll, we need to collect some information from you (including email address). We may use your email to send customer appreciation messages or to follow up or provide special offers based on your use of our website. You may change your preferences or withdraw your consent to receive such communications from London Drugs at any time.

When you opt in, we may use cookies or other technology to better understand your interests and to enhance and customize your use of our website and our communications with you. For more information on cookies see [Security & Cookie Policy](https://www.londondrugs.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-LondonDrugs-Site/default/Page-Show?cid=%20PrivacySecurity). You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases that may prevent you from using all the features on our Website or from receiving all the benefits otherwise provided when you opt in.

**London Drugs Wish List**  
The information provided by you to create your personal Wish List is collected and used by London Drugs to publish and maintain your Wish List as part of the London Drugs Wish List on our londondrugs.com website. The information we will collect from you will include, but not be limited to your name, contact information, event date & Wish List items. Some of this information will be displayed as part of your Wish List and members of the public will be able to view it. London Drugs may also use this information if we need to contact you regarding the London Drugs Wish List, your personal Wish List and any related matters thereto, such as changes to or purchases made from your Wish List, to advise you of any fulfillment or delivery matters or for follow up service matters. By creating your Wish List, you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set out above.

**Pharmacy**  
London Drugs has always been and will remain committed to keeping all your personal health information confidential. We recognize and appreciate your expectation that we ensure your privacy and confidentiality is maintained at all times. We take this responsibility extremely seriously. 

**Your personal health information includes:**

  * Name
  * Address
  * Telephone number
  * Date of birth
  * Personal Health Number (PHN), _if applicable_
  * Medical conditions
  * Medical allergies
  * Medication history

We use your personal health information to assist you with managing your medical condition, managing your health, and ensuring you receive the most appropriate medication and its respective dosage for you.

* * *

## We collect, use and disclose your personal health information in the following situations:

Personal health information (i.e. prescriptions) obtained by London Drugs will be used to dispense prescription medications.

  * We will document information related to the medications dispensed and services provided in your record.
  * We are required by law, in some provinces, to enter your personal health information in their respective provincial prescription computer systems. These systems monitor the prescription histories of all members of the population.
  * We may contact your prescribing doctor or healthcare professional to discuss with them your medication(s), strength of medication, instructions, and treatment options.
  * We may contact you to provide treatment-related services, such as refill reminders, treatment alternatives (i.e. available generic products), and other health-related benefits and services that may be of interest to you.
  * We may contact your health plan insurer, payor, or other agent and share your personal health information with that entity to enable them to accurately process the payment/reimbursement of your prescription and/or healthcare needs.
  * We may also contact you about a payment or balance due for prescriptions dispensed to you at a London Drugs pharmacy.
  * We may release your personal health information to you or an agent for you provided they produce written authorization from you.
  * We will only release the information specifically indicated in the authorization.
  * We may be required to release personal health information by court order or to regulatory bodies. 

* * *

## London Drugs Photolab

When you purchase a product or service from our photolab department, whether in-store, by kiosk, online through our website or by way of software download, you will need to provide us with contact and payment information so that we can process your request. You will of course also need to provide us with your digital and photographic images and content so we can fulfill the requested photo service.

The information you provide to us allows us to: ensure that you get the services and products you request, maintain your account, perform security and verification functions and contact you about the goods or services that you have ordered or may wish to obtain in the future (subject to your consent for this purpose).

We offer customers many products and services on our London Drugs online photo processing sites, including [www.londondrugs.com/photolab](https://photolab.londondrugs.com/) and [www.prolabcanada.ca](https://www.prolabcanada.ca/). In order to store, upload, download, view and share photos in these photo lab web sites, you must provide your email address and select a password to become a registered www.londondrugs.com/photolab user. This information enables us to maintain your photos securely in electronic storage, so only you and people you designate have access to them. It also allows us to establish and maintain your accounts, and for security and verification purposes. Registered users of the www.londondrugs.com/photolab site have the ability to view, update and change their personal profile within this site.

Users are responsible for ensuring verification information, including passwords, are protected and that you do not disclose them to other individuals. You are also responsible for ensuring that you understand any of the sharing functionality of the photolab service and that you use the service accordingly.

We use a third party service provider to assist us in providing certain photo services to you, subject to appropriate confidentiality and security measures. See heading ‘Disclosure to third party service providers’ in this Privacy policy for further details.

**Insurance Services Department of London Drugs Limited**   
The Insurance Services Department offers various forms of insurance and services, including auto insurance, travel insurance, pet insurance and home insurance. The Insurance Services Department collects information from you (both in person and on-line, should you request a quote on-line) in sufficient detail to provide you an insurance quote, process your insurance transaction, administer or renew your policy or otherwise provide the requested service. The Insurance Services Department acts as an agent for the actual insurance carriers and as such shares the information they obtain with the carriers in order to obtain quotes for you and to bind coverage if appropriate. 

Because the Insurance Services Department is a licensed insurance agency, and its employees and representatives include licensed insurance adjusters, agents and salespersons, in addition to existing privacy laws, it also complies with any additional privacy obligations set out by the Insurance Councils of BC and Alberta and ICBC, in the case of ICBC Autoplan coverage.

**Call centre**   
London Drugs operates a call centre to respond to customer's questions, concerns, complaints and suggestions for service improvement. These suggestions and complaints are important to us as it enables us to provide better service to you our customers. As part of this process we may collect caller’s name, phone number, email and other information that they choose to give us, in order to appropriately respond to customer. However we will only ever collect personal information that you choose to voluntarily provide to us when connected with our call centre. Customers are always free to ask questions, voice concerns, make complaints and provide suggestions without giving us any personal information. We value all such suggestions.

**Cosmetics**  
London Drugs is committed to protecting your personal information while ensuring that we have the tools required to provide you with a superior shopping experience.

In our cosmetics department we have several vendor-sponsored rewards programs that may include a component where we ask for your contact information so we can administer the program. London Drugs or our vendor partner may ask you to opt into a mailing list for additional marketing information and/or special offers. Your consent is not a condition of you participating in the reward program.

From time to time, we may also have promotions or surveys within the Cosmetics department, which are supported by our vendor partners. If you choose to participate, you may be asked for contact information as well as additional optional survey information (for example, product preferences). You may also be asked by either London Drugs or the vendor to provide your consent to be added to promotional mailings and newsletters. Your consent is not a condition of you participating in the promotion.

When returning a product to our cosmetics department you may be asked for contact information as well as information as to why you are returning a specific product. This may be disclosed to the vendor and is used by the vendor to improve their product. You may also be asked by either London Drugs or the vendor to provide your consent to be added to promotional mailings and newsletters. Your consent related to promotional mailings or newsletters is not a condition of receiving your refund.

**Rebates**  
Certain products sold within London Drugs may be eligible for rebates. To receive your rebate, you may be required by either London Drugs or the vendor to provide your proof of purchase in addition to contact information such as name and address. Your consent may also be requested in order to send you promotional mailings and newsletters. Your consent is not a condition of receiving the rebate.

**In store activations**  
As a service to our customers London Drugs may offer to activate various products and services within our retail stores: these products may include cellular phones, ADSL services, and satellite services. When performing these in-store activations on behalf of our customers, we may be required to collect specific personal information which is then provided to the respective service providers. London Drugs does not retain or use the information provided to these service providers.

**Flyer/SuperFlyer/Catalogue Delivery**  
If you call us to report the non-delivery of your London Drugs Flyers, SuperFlyers and/or Catalogues, in order to resolve your complaint we will ask for your: name, address, postal code and telephone number.

This information will be provided to the distributor responsible for delivery in your area to resolve the problem. Neither London Drugs nor the distributor will retain or use this information for any reason other than ensuring delivery of our Flyer/SuperFlyer and/or catalogues.

In the unlikely event that we cannot resolve a delivery concern, with your permission we will provide your Name, Address & Postal Code to a Mailing Supplier that will send our Flyer, SuperFlyer and/or Catalogues to you by addressed mail. Neither London Drugs nor the Mailing Supplier will use this information for any other reason than mailing you our Flyer/SuperFlyer and/or catalogues.

**Contests, promotions and surveys**  
From time to time our vendor partners may run contests or promotions within our stores either by way of specific contest entry forms or by coupons enclosed within products. We encourage you to read and understand the contest rules for each of these contests and promotions.

In addition, London Drugs may also run contests or promotions which may be available on-line or in the store. All contests are subject to rules that will be available with each particular contest. Should you choose to participate, you will be asked for contact information which will only be used to contact you should you win, unless you otherwise consent.

London Drugs contest and promotion forms may also ask additional optional survey questions in order that we may improve our product and service offerings. Your participation in answering the optional questions is not a condition of entering any contest or promotion.

London Drugs may also conduct surveys via our websites, email or in store, participation in which is always optional to customer. Information collected in such surveys will only be used to better understood customer needs, preferences and opinions and how London Drugs can provide the best possible service, value and products to our customers.

**Customer Reviews**  
The Customer Review and Ask & Answer features on our website are provided as a service to our customers. While London Drugs does not provide any of your personal information to our third party service provider managing these features on our behalf, your reviews, questions and answers will be provided and may be accessible to all visitors to our website – so please do not include any personal information as part of your reviews/questions/answers.

**Our LDExtras Program**  
In order to participate in our LDExtras Program (the “Program”), you will need to register and provide certain information, such as: name, email, phone number, gender, birthdate, address (city, province & postal code) and, at your option, street address and certain preferences and interests. This information is collected in order to administer and manage your participation in the Program, to communicate with you about the Program, as well as to personalize and improve your Program experience.

You will have the option to receive additional Program communications, including via email, intended to maximize the benefits and value members will enjoy from the Program. Such communications may contain the Extras you earn, program status updates, as well as special promotions, offers, events and news. These are only for Program members and are different from emails or e-newsletters you may otherwise receive from London Drugs, which you may separately opt out of at any time. Note that even if you decide not to receive additional Program emails, members may still receive some emails necessary for the administration of the Program. You can register for the LDExtras Program or unsubscribe at any time at: www.ldextras.com.

Through the Program, personal information is collected from members in the following ways: (i) information voluntarily provided by members, such as when you register to become a Program member as set out above; and (ii) when a member uses his or her member identifier number (usually their phone number) to make a purchase at a London Drugs store or online at www.londondrugs.com, certain transaction data is collected and will form part of that member’s profile. Transaction data collected may include without limit: date/time/location/value/product and type of purchase. Such data is used to accrue benefits in the form of LDExtras to members, but also may be used to provide personalized and exclusive offers and benefits for that member and to better understand and serve customers of London Drugs generally.

Under strict conditions and safeguards, London Drugs may allow access to member information to trusted vendors, partners and service providers for the purpose of assisting London Drugs to administer and improve the Program and providing members with Extras, to better understand member interests and preferences, and expand and improve upon services offered to members through the Program; as well as to improve product recommendations, online user experience and provide new or improved services, benefits or offers while on www.londondrugs.com (which may require Member to also have has an account with www.londondrugs.com). 

Anonymized or aggregated data of members may be used by London Drugs and accessed by trusted partners for analytic purposes, to better understand customer behavior and preferences, to improve how London Drugs merchandises and promotes products; to measure success of promotional offers and events; and to create more meaningful shopping experiences, offers, marketing and promotional events for customers.

For more information on the Program, please go to [www.ldextras.com](https://www.ldextras.com/). 

**Push Notifications on Mobile Apps**   
Where any mobile applications provided by London Drugs (including our LDExtras App or RX App) (“mobile app”) allow for the delivery of "push notifications" or texts, you may expressly opt in to receive such notifications when you register for our mobile app or subsequently through the settings found either within our mobile app or on your mobile device. You may withdraw your consent for push notifications at any time by toggling off the "notifications" switch within the settings of our mobile app or by locating our mobile app in the settings of your mobile device and unclicking or unchecking notifications. 

**Our Websites**  
All references to our ”Website” or “Websites” in this Policy include all websites owned and operated by London Drugs Limited, including without limit: www.londondrugs.com (including [photolab.londondrugs.com](https://photolab.londondrugs.com/) and [pharmacy.londondrugs.com](https://pharmacy.londondrugs.com/); [www.ldinsurance.ca](https://www.ldinsurance.ca/); [www.ldhealth.com](https://www.ldhealth.com/); [www.ldextras.com](https://www.ldextras.com/) and [www.prolabcanada.ca](https://www.prolabcanada.ca/). Specific privacy policies, terms of use and information related to these websites may be found on each of those sites.

**Live Chat** – At your option, you can message and live chat digitally with London Drugs through our website. The chats are monitored and recorded with the assistance of our service provider. This allows you to print or request a transcript of the chat by email for easy reference to products, services or other information provided during the chat. 

Like most websites, London Drugs directly or via trusted service providers, may track certain Website usage information in a manner which does not personally identify you. Such information may include use of Websites (such as geolocation, web pages visited, time on each page), services, software, browser type and history, meta data, operational meta data, and other related information such as IP addresses and types of device used. Such information may be used to analyze trends, administer the services, track users' movement for analytics, including purchasing and online behavior and activities, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, as well as to help improve the content, administration and delivery of services and understand how our customers prefer to use our services. We may use various forms of technology to achieve this, including cookies, javascript tags and pixels. Please see our [Security & Cookie Policy](https://www.londondrugs.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-LondonDrugs-Site/default/Page-Show?cid=%20PrivacySecurity) for more information. 

**Disclosure to and from third party service providers**  
London Drugs uses third party service providers to assist in delivering, managing and improving various aspects of our business operations, including the operation of our website and the services we provide to our valued customers. 

In some cases, London Drugs needs to share customer personal information with its service providers. Some examples of the type of situations where this may occur are set out elsewhere in this policy and include (but are not limited to): to provide you with products and services you have requested; to operate and maintain our websites and online and ecommerce activities; to facilitate product warranty, repair, return, recall and customer service requests or issues; for order fulfillment purposes; to send requested marketing communications; to enable financial and credit card transactions; to administer our LDExtras Program; to provide enhanced product recommendations and services while online; to enable digital communication with you through chat, messaging and other methods; to verify and validate information that you have provided and for fraud prevention; and to transmit, process or host certain photofinishing services. 

Whenever London Drugs shares personal information with third party service providers, we use contractual and other appropriate means to help ensure your personal information is used in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable laws. If you do not wish us to provide your personal information to a service provider we may be unable to process the transaction or provide our services to you. 

In some cases, our service providers or their servers are located in jurisdictions outside of Canada. Where personal information is provided by London Drugs to such a service provider, your information may then be stored or processed outside of Canada, including the United States. Service providers located outside of Canada may be required to disclose personal information to law enforcement or regulatory authorities under the laws of their jurisdiction. 

**General**  
All the information you provide to us is securely maintained and is kept strictly confidential to a level appropriate to the level of sensitivity of the information. We use a variety of security measures such as restricting employee access to files, data centers, and using locked file cabinets. In addition we make use of electronic security measures such as passwords, personal ID numbers and data encryption as appropriate. 

Employees must conform to London Drugs Privacy Code and observe the highest standards of confidentiality. We subscribe to the general principle that only those employees that need to know the information in order to provide you services have access to your information. 

Where the word “including” is used in this policy, it means “including but not limited to” and is not intended to be an exhaustive listing. 

* * *

## London Drugs may disclose your information as permitted or required by law: Examples of this include:

  * to comply with a subpoena, warrant or order issued or made by a court, person or body with jurisdiction to compel the production of personal information
  * to an entity, which may be a government institution or other person that has lawful authority to obtain the information
  * to a public body or a law enforcement agency concerning an offence under the laws of Canada or a province, to our internal or external legal counsel.

**Security**  
We work very hard to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide on all of our Websites. Please see our [Security & Cookie policy](https://www.londondrugs.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-LondonDrugs-Site/default/Page-Show?cid=%20PrivacySecurity) for further details.

**Cookies and other Computer Information**  
See our [Security & Cookie Policy](https://www.londondrugs.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-LondonDrugs-Site/default/Page-Show?cid=%20PrivacySecurity) for more information about how we use cookies and other tracking technology on our Websites.

**When is my information removed?**  
We keep your personal information on file as long as we need it to provide you with a service and to meet legal requirements. When it is no longer needed we destroy the information or render it anonymous. Should you desire, you can contact our Chief Privacy Officer and request that we remove your information from our records. We will make every reasonable effort to honour your request, however, we may retain some information you have requested to remove to prevent fraud, collect moneys owed, resolve disputes, and to comply with federal and provincial legal requirements.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
Our business constantly changes to meet the needs of our customers and as a result our policies and procedures pertaining to privacy and security are also subject to change. We reserve the right at any time to change, update, add or remove any of our practices, policies and procedures which relate to privacy, at any time without prior notice. It is your responsibility to periodically check this Privacy Policy, as well as our other online terms and policies for changes, which shall be effective as of their date of posting.

**Chief Privacy Officer**  
London Drugs has appointed a senior member of their management group to the role of Chief Privacy Officer. It is this person's role to ensure that London Drugs meets our customers' expectations surrounding privacy. If you have questions or concerns regarding London Drugs Privacy Policy please contact us: 

**By mail:**  
Chief Privacy Officer  
London Drugs Limited  
12831 Horseshoe Place, Richmond, BC V7A 4X5

**By phone:**  
Monday to Friday [except holidays] 8:30 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. PST Phone: (604) 448-1055  
Or toll free 1 (866) 805-8283 (within Canada)  
Fax: (604) 272-4623

**By e-mail:**  

* * *

## Other Privacy Resources on the Web

The Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner for British Columbia  

The Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner of Alberta  

Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada  

**How can I access my information?**  
You may access and verify your information and find out to whom we have disclosed it to at any time by contacting us at [privacy@londondrugs.com](mailto:privacy@londondrugs.com). There may be a nominal cost for this service. At the time of your request, we will need specific information from you to verify your identity before we can provide you with the requested information.

* * *

## Upon receiving such a request, London Drugs will:

  * Inform you about what type of personal information we have on record, how it is used and to whom it may have been disclosed
  * Provide you with reasonable access to your information so you can review and verify the accuracy and completeness and request changes to the information
  * Make any necessary updates and amendments to your personal information
  * There may be instances when we will not be able to provide you with access to all of the Personal Information that you have requested. Examples are if the information
  * Contains references to other persons
  * Has already been destroyed in accordance with our policy of only keeping your information for as long as it is needed
  * Is subject to solicitor-client or litigation privilege
  * You may also contact our Chief Privacy Officer at any time to let us know that you do not wish to receive any further communication from us or to ask us to change your preferences regarding how we use or disclose your information.

**If you have a complaint or a question for us**  
We are committed to setting the highest customer service standard within the retail industry. We hope you give us the opportunity to correct any situation that does not meet your expectations. If you have any concerns about privacy, confidentiality or our policies and procedures we want to know about it. All inquiries relating to personal information will receive prompt attention and be acknowledged within 5 business days.

* * *

## It's all about trust

We will continuously assess ourselves to ensure that customer privacy is respected. We will conduct our business in a manner that meets the expectations of our customers in the many communities in which we do business.
